<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<root>
    <!-- These are specifically user-facing changes and thus do not need detail about inner workings of FunkyBot. Changes to jokes and pics do not need to be noted unless significant. -->

    <version num="2.0.0">
        <change>All commands now use a different syntax. Instead of using double brackets `[[like this]]`, arguments must be in single brackets `[like this]`. For commands that take multiple arguments, each argument must be in its own set of brackets `[like][this]`. Each argument can be anywhere in your message, even if there are words in between them.</change>
        <change>`!remind` and `!announce` now accept more different date formats. You can now use two-digit years and omit the date argument altogether, and timezones are now accepted as UTC offsets in hours (e.g. +8.5 or -6 instead of +0850 or -0600). Send `!help [!remind]` or `!help [!announce]` for details.</change>
        <change>The command list from sending `!help` is now much easier to read.</change>
        <change>Embeds from the `!magic` command are now colored according to their card's color identity.</change>
        <change>You can now search for a Magic card from a specific set by adding a `|` and the set code like `!magic [Lightning Bolt|STA]`. Send `!help [!magic]` for more details.</change>
        <change>The `!calc` command now better distinguishes negative numbers from subtraction, can read implicit multiplication (for example, `2(2)`), and can now calculate absolute value `abs()` and base 10 logarithms `log()`.</change>
        <change>Fixed `!remind` and `!announce` to correctly accept time between 12:00 and 12:59 AM or PM.</change>
    </version>

    <version num="1.9.0">
        <change>Added the `!calc` command to calculate equations. To learn more, send `!help [[!calc]]`.</change>
        <change>When sending an unknown command, you can now send `!yes` to automatically use the provided suggestion.</change>
        <change>Separated `!remind` command into `!remind` and `!time`. `!remind` and `!announce` now only support date arguments, while `!time` only supports time arguments.</change>
        <change>`!remind` and `!announce` commands are now more flexible with the formatting of arguments they accept.</change>
        <change>Fixed a bug where `!roll` command wouldn't work with an argument of `2`.</change>
        <change>Fixed a bug where reminders and announcements wouldn't trigger after FunkyBot resets.</change>
    </version>

    <version num="1.8.6">
        <change>Feedback added when a user enters an incorrect command.</change>
        <change>`!magic` now provides price information in USD.</change>
        <change>Made `!cute` and `!react` commands less likely to post images recently posted using them.</change>
    </version>

    <version num="1.8.5">
        <change>`!binary` and `!hex` commands can now convert up to three numbers.</change>
        <change>`!roll` can now roll up to five dice. If more than one die roll is requested, your total roll will be displayed.</change>
        <change>Polls now run for three hours instead of one.</change>
        <change>Slightly changed the possible answers for the `!ask` command to make noncommittal answers less common.</change>
    </version>      

    <version num="1.8.4">
        <change>Improved feedback for user when using the `!remind` or `!announce` commands</change>
        <change>Replaced message sent with the `!hello` command with an embed containing more information</change>
        <change>Added Discord status to FunkyBot to display '!help'</change>
        <change>Changed links from `!magic` and `!wiki` commands to be in the embed rather than the message</change>
    </version>
  
</root>
