<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<root>
    <!-- Informational commands -->
    <function category="information">
        <command>hello</command>
        <format>!hello</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!hello` to see some information about me.</description>
            <hint>Using this command, you can see my version number, a list of recent changes, and the time I've been working.</hint>
        </body>
    </function>

    <function category="information">
        <command>help</command>
        <format>!help [X]</format>
        <body>
            <description>This is the command you're using! Send `!help [X]` to have me explain a command in detail.</description>
            <hint>You can also send just the name of the command without the ! character.</hint>
            <hint>I can only send an explanation of one command at a time.</hint>
            <hint>For commands with arguments in brackets, you just need to send the name of the command. Don't send any brackets.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to get an explanation of the `!binary` command, you should send: `!help [!binary]`.</hint>
        </body>
        <body>
            <description>You can also send `!help` with no arguments to get a list of commands.</description>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure the command you want help with is surrounded by brackets. If you want a list of all commands, don't send any brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">I need a command to search for. If you want a list of all commands, don't send any brackets.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only search for one command at a time.</error>
        <error type="bad_command">I don't have the command you're searching for. If you want a list of all commands, send `!help` with no arguments.</error>
    </function>

    <!-- Useful commands -->
    <function category="useful">
        <command>announce</command>
        <format>!announce [X]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!announce [X]` to have me send everyone a notification at the specified date.</description>
            <hint>You must supply the date, time, and timezone in that order.</hint>
            <hint>Your argument should be formatted as `MM/DD/YYYY HH:MM TZ`.</hint>
            <hint>If you don't provide a date, I will use the time you provide with the current date based on the timezone you send.</hint> 
            <hint>If you use a 12 hour clock, you can add specify AM or PM after a space. If you don't specify, I will use AM unless it's a 24 hour clock.</hint>
            <hint>Timezone should be the UTC offset in hours `(+/-)HH`.</hint>
            <hint>I can only set an announcement for one date at a time.</hint>
            <hint>You can set a custom message by typing anywhere in the message outside of the brackets.</hint>
            <hint>Only server administrators can use this command.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to set an announcement for your birthday party on May 21, 2021 at 2:30 PM US Mountain Time, send: `!announce [05/20/2021 14:30 -6] birthday party`.</hint>
            <hint>This would also work: `!announce [5/20/21 2:30 PM -6] birthday party`.</hint>
            <hint>If you wanted to have the announcement happen the same day you set it, you could send this: `!announce [2:30 PM -6] birthday party`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure the date you want me to use to set your announcement is surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">I need a date to set your announcement for.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only set an announcement for one date at a time.</error>
        <error type="bad_date">Make sure your date argument is in the proper format: `MM/DD/YYYY HH:MM (+/-)TZ`.</error>
        <error type="negative_date">Announcements must be set for a date in the future.</error>
    </function>

    <function category="useful">
        <command>binary</command>
        <format>!binary [X][...]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!binary [X]` to have me convert your numbers to binary.</description>
            <hint>I can convert up to {binary_max_args} numbers.</hint>
            <hint>I can only convert numbers 0-65535.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to convert 5 to binary, you should send: `!binary [5]`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure the numbers you want me to convert are surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">I need a number to convert.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only convert at most {binary_max_args} numbers at a time.</error>
        <error type="bad_value">I can only convert integers to binary.</error>
        <error type="bad_number">I can only convert numbers 0-65535 to binary.</error>
    </function>

    <function category="useful">
        <command>calc</command>
        <format>!calc [X]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!calc [X]` to have me calculate an equation for you.</description>
            <hint>I can only calculate one equation at a time.</hint>
            <hint>You can use positive and negative integers or decimals as operands.</hint>
            <hint>I can use the following operators: `+`, `-`, `*`, `/`, `^` (exponent).</hint>
            <hint>I can use the following functions: `sqrt()` (square root), `abs()` (absolute value), and `log()` (log base 10).</hint>
            <hint>You can use parentheses, just make sure open and closed perentheses are matched.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to calculate 6 plus the square root of 4, you should send: `!calc [6 + sqrt(4)]`</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure the equation you want me to calculate is surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">I need an equation to calculate.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only calculate one equation at a time.</error>
        <error type="bad_tokens">I can only calculate using numbers, operators, and the sqrt, abs, and log functions.</error>
        <error type="missing_operand">Each operator needs an operand on its left and right.</error>
        <error type="few_operators">There are not enough operators or functions for me to use on the operands.</error>
        <error type="open_perens">Make sure every open parenthesis has a matching closed parenthesis and vice versa.</error>
        <error type="too_many_operators">There are too many operators for the operands you gave me.</error>
    </function>

    <function category="useful">
        <command>game</command>
        <format>!game [X]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!game [X]` to have me search Giant Bomb for a video game.</description>
            <hint>I can only search for one game at a time.</hint>
            <hint>If you didn't get quite what you were searching for, I will also give you a link to the full search on Giant Bomb's website.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to search for Minecraft, you should send: `!game [Minecraft]`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure the game you want me to search for is surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">I need a game to search for.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only search for one game at a time.</error>
    </function>

    <function category="useful">
        <command>hex</command>
        <format>!hex [X][...]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!hex [X]` to have me convert your numbers to hexadecimal.</description>
            <hint>I can convert up to {hex_max_args} numbers.</hint>
            <hint>I can only convert numbers 0-65535.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to convert 5 to hexadecimal, you should send: `!hex [5]`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure the numbers you want me to convert is surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">I need a number to convert.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only convert at most {hex_max_args} numbers at a time.</error>
        <error type="bad_value">I can only convert integers to hexadecimal.</error>
        <error type="bad_number">I can only convert numbers 0-65535 to hexadecimal.</error>
    </function>

    <function category="useful">
        <command>magic</command>
        <format>!magic [X][...]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!magic [X]` to have me search Scryfall for a Magic: The Gathering card.</description>
            <hint>I can search for up to three cards.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to search for Island, you should send: `!magic [island]`.</hint>
            <hint>I can also search for a random card using the word "random". For example: `!magic [random]`.</hint>
            <hint>You can also use Scryfall's syntax to narrow down possible cards when searching for a random card. For example, to search for a random red and green commander, you should send: `!magic [random c=rg is:commander]`.</hint>
            <hint>You can also search for a specific printing of a card by adding `|` and a set code. If I can't find that specific printing, I'll ignore it and search for your card anyway. For example, to search for Lightning Bolt from 4th Edition, you should send `!magic [Lightning Bolt|4ED]`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure the cards you want me to search for are surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">You must put something in the brackets.</error>
        <error type="too_few">I need a card to search for.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only search for at most {magic_max_args} cards at a time.</error>
    </function>

    <function category="useful">
        <command>poll</command>
        <format>!poll [X][Y][...]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!poll [X][Y]` to have me start a poll with the given options.</description>
            <hint>When the poll is running, people can vote on the choices by increasing the corresponding reactions that I add to the poll message. Adding new reactions will not do anything.</hint>
            <hint>The poll will automatically be open for {poll_max_duration} hours, but you can end it early by sending `!end` in the same channel.</hint>
            <hint>When the poll is concluded, I will display the results.</hint>
            <hint>You can set a custom poll question by typing anywhere in the message outside of the brackets.</hint>
            <hint>I need at least two options, but you can send up to five.</hint>
            <hint>You can only run a single poll per channel at a time.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to poll people on what their favorite color is, send: `!poll What is your favorite color? [Red][Yellow][Blue]`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure each option you want on the poll are surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">You must put something in the brackets.</error>
        <error type="too_few">I need at least two poll options for people to vote on.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only set up to five options for people to vote on.</error>
    </function>

    <function category="useful">
        <command>remind</command>
        <format>!remind [X]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!remind [X]` to have me send you a notification at the specified date.</description>
            <hint>You must supply the date, time, and timezone in that order.</hint>
            <hint>Your argument should be formatted as `MM/DD/YYYY HH:MM TZ`.</hint>
            <hint>If you don't provide a date, I will use the time you provide with the current date based on the timezone you send.</hint> 
            <hint>If you use a 12 hour clock, you can add specify AM or PM after a space. If you don't specify, I will use AM unless it's a 24 hour clock.</hint>
            <hint>Timezone should be the UTC offset in hours `(+/-)HH`.</hint>
            <hint>I can only set a reminder for one date at a time.</hint>
            <hint>You can set a custom message by typing anywhere in the message outside of the brackets.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to set a reminder for a friend's birthday party on May 21, 2021 at 2:30 PM US Mountain Time, send: `!remind [05/20/2021 14:30 -6] birthday party`.</hint>
            <hint>This would also work: `!remind [5/20/21 2:30 PM -6] birthday party`.</hint>
            <hint>If you wanted to have the reminder happen the same day you set it, you could send this: `!remind [2:30 PM -6] birthday party`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure the date you want me to use to set your reminder is surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">I need a date to set your reminder for.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only set a reminder for one date at a time.</error>
        <error type="bad_date">Make sure your date argument is in the proper format: `MM/DD/YYYY HH:MM (+/-)TZ`.</error>
        <error type="negative_date">Reminders must be set for a date in the future.</error>
    </function>

    <function category="useful">
        <command>roll</command>
        <format>!roll [X][...]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!roll [X]` to have me roll a die with X sides.</description>
            <hint>I can roll up to {roll_max_args} dice.</hint>
            <hint>If you send me multiple dice I will also tell you the total roll.</hint>
            <hint>Each die must have at least 2 sides (I guess that's just a coin?) and can have up to 1000 sides.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to roll a 6-sided dice, you should send: `!roll [6]`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure the number of sides of each die is surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">I need a number of sides to roll a die.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only roll at most {roll_max_args} dice at a time.</error>
        <error type="bad_value">I can only roll dice with an integer number of sides.</error>
        <error type="bad_number">I can only roll dice with 2-1000 sides.</error>
    </function>

    <function category="useful">
        <command>time</command>
        <format>!time [X][...]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!time [X]` to have me send you a notification after the set time.</description>
            <hint>Time can be set with s(econds), h(ours), and d(ays).</hint>
            <hint>Time cannot exceed {time_max_duration} days.</hint>
            <hint>Each unit of time must be in separate brackets.</hint>
            <hint>I need at least one argument but I can take up to three.</hint>
            <hint>You can set a custom message by typing anywhere in the message outside of the brackets.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to remind yourself to go to sleep in two and a half hours, send: `!time [2h][30m] go to sleep`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure each time unit you want me to use to set your timer is surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only take three arguments.</error>
        <error type="too_few">I need at least one argument to set your reminder.</error>
        <error type="bad_duration">Make sure your arguments use only integers and use letters to set s(econds), h(ours), or d(ays).</error>
        <error type="too_long">Time cannot exceed {time_max_duration} days.</error>
        <error type="empty">You must put something in the brackets.</error>
	    <error type="no_duration">The time for the reminder to run must last at least one second.</error>
    </function>

    <function category="useful">
        <command>wiki</command>
        <format>!wiki [X]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!wiki [X]` to have me search for a Wikipedia article.</description>
            <hint>I can only search for one article at a time.</hint>
            <hint>I can't screen the content I find, so please don't break server rules by searching for certain articles!</hint>
            <hint>For example, to search for "shiba inu," you should send: `!wiki [Shiba Inu]`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure the article you want me to search for is surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">I need an article to search for.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only search for one article at a time.</error>
    </function>

    <!-- Fun commands -->
    <function category="fun">
        <command>ask</command>
        <format>!ask</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!ask` to get a yes or no answer to something.</description>
        </body>
    </function>

    <function category="fun">
        <command>choose</command>
        <format>!choose [X][Y][...]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!choose [X][Y]` to have me choose from your options.</description>
            <hint>I need at least 2 choices to choose from, but you can send up to {choose_max_args}.</hint>
            <hint>Make sure each option is in its own set of brackets.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to choose from cats or dogs, you should send: `!choose [cats][dogs]`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure each option you want me to choose from are surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">At least one of the arguments you gave me was empty.</error>
        <error type="too_few">I need at least two things to choose from.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only choose from at most {choose_max_args} things at a time.</error>
    </function>

    <function category="fun">
        <command>cute</command>
        <format>!cute</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!cute` to have me send a random cute animal picture.</description>
        </body>
    </function>

    <function category="fun">
        <command>joke</command>
        <format>!joke</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!joke` to have me send a one-liner joke. Laughs are not guaranteed.</description>
        </body>
    </function>

    <function category="fun">
        <command>react</command>
        <format>!react</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!react` to have me send a random reaction image.</description>
        </body>
    </function>

    <function category="fun">
        <command>rate</command>
        <format>!rate</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!rate [X]` to have me rate something on a scale from 1 to 10.</description>
            <hint>I can only rate one thing at a time.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to rate Discord, you should send: `!rate [Discord]`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="brackets">Make sure the thing you want me to rate is surrounded by brackets.</error>
        <error type="empty">I need something to rate.</error>
        <error type="too_many">I can only rate one thing at a time.</error>
    </function>

    <function category="fun">
        <command>rps</command>
        <format>!rps [X]</format>
        <body>
            <description>Send `!rps [X]` to play rock paper scissors with me.</description>
            <hint>You must use `rock`, `paper`, or `scissors` as your argument.</hint>
            <hint>You can only send one choice at a time.</hint>
            <hint>For example, to play rock paper scissors with paper as your choice, send `!rps [paper]`.</hint>
        </body>
        <error type="empty">I need an option to play against.</error>
        <error type="too_many">You can only play against one option at a time.</error>
    </function>

    <!-- Contextual commands -->
    <!-- These only have function in specific contexts. They will not show up in the command list. -->
    <function category="contextual">
        <command>yes</command>
        <format>!yes</format>
        <body>
            <description>Confirms pending reminders or announcements made by the user.</description>
        </body>
    </function>

    <function category="contextual">
        <command>no</command>
        <format>!no</format>
        <body>
            <description>Denies pending reminders or announcements made by the user.</description>
        </body>
    </function>

    <function category="contextual">
        <command>end</command>
        <format>!end</format>
        <body>
            <description>Ends the user's current poll in the channel prematurely.</description>
        </body>
    </function>
</root>