<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<root>
    <list type="answers">
        <answer>Yes.</answer>
        <answer>Certainly.</answer>
        <answer>Probably.</answer>
        <answer>I suppose so.</answer>
        <answer>Of course!</answer>
        <answer>Absolutely definitely 100% yes.</answer>
        <answer>Yepperoni.</answer>
        <answer>I'd say yes.</answer>
        <answer>01111001 01100101 01110011 (yes)</answer>
        <answer>answer == "yes"</answer>
        <answer>Ask again later.</answer>
        <answer>It's better for now if you don't know.</answer>
        <answer>IDK</answer>
        <answer>I'm not telling.</answer>
        <answer>404: Answer not found.</answer>
        <answer>No.</answer>
        <answer>Yeah, I'm gonna say no on that one.</answer>
        <answer>Nope. No way. Negative. Absolutely not.</answer>
        <answer>No way!</answer>
        <answer>Nooooooope.</answer>
    </list>

    <list type="jokes">
        <joke>Shout out to anyone wondering what the opposite of in is.</joke>
        <joke>Remains to be seen if glass coffins become popular.</joke>
        <joke>A joke becomes a dad joke when the punchline is apparent.</joke>
        <joke>I just accidentally swallowed a bunch of Scrabble tiles. My next trip to the bathroom could spell disaster.</joke>
        <joke>My friend keeps annoying me with bird puns. Well toucan play at that game!</joke>
        <joke>The sweater I bought from the store was picking up too much static, so I returned it to the store and they gave me another free of charge.</joke>
        <joke>I was wondering why the baseball was getting bigger. Then it hit me.</joke>
        <joke>Not only is my thesaurus bad, it's also bad!</joke>
        <joke>There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary and those who don't.</joke>
        <joke>This coffee tastes like boiled dirt, but it was just ground this morning!</joke>
        <joke>Whiteboards are remarkable!</joke>
        <joke>People used to laugh when I said I wanted to be a comedian. Well nobody's laughing now!</joke>
        <joke>I really should sell my vaccuum cleaner. It's just gathering dust.</joke>
        <joke>So a man walks into a bar. That must have hurt.</joke>
        <joke>Scientists say reducing my body temperature to -273.15 degrees C would kill me, but I think I would be 0K.</joke>
        <joke>Rene Descartes walks into a bar. The bartender asks if he wants a drink. He says, "I think not" and disappears.</joke>
        <joke>Helium walks into a bar. The bartender says, "we don't serve noble gases here." He didn't react.</joke>
        <joke>You hear about that band, "1023 MB"? They haven't had any gigs yet.</joke>
        <joke>Did you hear about the guy whose left arm was cut off? He's alright now.</joke>
        <joke>An infinite number of guys walk into a bar. The first says, "I'll have a beer." The second says, "I'll have half of a beer." The third says, "I'll have a quarter of a beer..." The bartender pulls out two beers and tells them to know their limits.</joke>
        <joke>A policeman pulls over Werner Heisenberg and asks him, "do you know how fast you were going?" Heisenberg replies, "no, but I know where I am."</joke>
        <joke>Why do scuba divers fall backwards off the boat? Because if they fell forward, they'd still be on the boat.</joke>
        <joke>I don't always tell dad jokes. But when I do, he laughs.</joke>
        <joke>What do you get when you cross a joke and a rhetorical question?</joke>
        <joke>Use plenty of fresh Avogadros to make some tasty guacamol.</joke>
        <joke>An 18-wheeler full of wigs and toupees crashed and spilled over the interstate at 1:30 today. Police are still combing the area.</joke>
        <joke>A man is currently in the hospital after he swallowed $115 worth of bills. No change is expected.</joke>
        <joke>Someone reportedly stole all of the toilets at the local police station. The police would open investigation but they have nothing to go on.</joke>
        <joke>Two fish are in a tank. One turns to the other and says "you man the guns, I'll drive!"</joke>
        <joke>So a termite walks into a bar and asks the bartender, "where is the bar tender?"</joke>
        <joke>Why did the capacitor kiss the diode? He just couldn’t resistor!</joke>
        <joke>I bought a locket today and put my own picture in it. Now I'm really independent!</joke>
        <joke>An anagram for "Banach-Tarski" is "Banach-Tarski Banach-Tarski."</joke>
        <joke>Elevators are ok, I guess. They have their ups and downs.</joke>
        <joke>Building stairs is rewarding, but it is a step-by-step process.</joke>
        <joke>A programmer was about to leave for an errand when his wife asks him, "while you're out, could you pick up eggs?" The man never returned.</joke>
        <joke>I poured root beer into a square glass, and now I just have beer.</joke>
        <joke>I wasn't originally going to get a brain transplant, but then I changed my mind.</joke>
        <joke>I recently ordered a thesaurus online and when it arrived the pages were totally blank. I have no words to describe how angry I am.</joke>
        <joke>I once stayed up all night trying to figure out where the sun went. Then it dawned on me.</joke>
        <joke>I love my ceiling. It's not the best but it's definitely up there.</joke>
        <joke>The shovel was a groundbreaking invention.</joke>
        <joke>The definition of opaque is not clear.</joke>
        <joke>Shoutout to sidewalks for keeping me off the street.</joke>
        <joke>I'm terrified of elevators. I'm going to take steps to avoid them.</joke>
        <joke>A woman reported her baggage stolen and the detective found it within the hour. It turns out it was a brief case.</joke>
        <joke>I have an intense fear of speed bumps, but I'm slowly getting over it.</joke>
        <joke>I took the shell off of my racing snail to make him faster, but it just ended up making him more sluggish.</joke>
        <joke>I'm dedicating my life to finding a cure for insomnia. I won't rest until I do!</joke>
    </list>

    <list type="ratings">
        <rating>
	    <rank>1</rank>
            <descriptor>Why would you even have me rate this?</descriptor>
        </rating>
        <rating>
            <rank>2</rank>
            <descriptor>I've seen worse I suppose.</descriptor>
        </rating>
        <rating>
            <rank>3</rank>
            <descriptor>It is passable at best.</descriptor>
        </rating>
        <rating>
            <rank>4</rank>
            <descriptor>If I had no other options, it would be okay.</descriptor>
        </rating>
        <rating>
            <rank>5</rank>
            <descriptor>Painfully average.</descriptor>
        </rating>
        <rating>
            <rank>6</rank>
            <descriptor>Could be better, could be worse.</descriptor>
        </rating>
        <rating>
            <rank>7</rank>
            <descriptor>This is acceptable.</descriptor>
        </rating>
        <rating>
            <rank>8</rank>
            <descriptor>You know what? That's pretty good.</descriptor>
        </rating>
        <rating>
            <rank>9</rank>
            <descriptor>What a great thing this is!</descriptor>
        </rating>
        <rating>
            <rank>10</rank>
            <descriptor>I have never seen anything better in my life. Fantastic!</descriptor>
        </rating>
    </list>
</root>